A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, RG 44 FA253
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, RG 44
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David
FA253
44.93 Cubic Feet 42 standard record storage boxes.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 44
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetically arranged in 36 series primarily by subject/topic.
Biographical / Historical
The central figure in the creation and operation of the Standard Oil Company during its rise to the top of the petroleum industry, John D. Rockefeller (JDR) established for the family a leading role in business and philanthropy. From the days of his earliest employment, Rockefeller, a devout Baptist, was generous in his giving to worthy causes, especially those of a religious nature. During the 1890s he developed an orderly system of philanthropic giving through an office staff that included his close advisor, Frederick T. Gates (1853-1929) and his son, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (1874-1960). With the advise of these and other associates, Rockefeller established the University of Chicago, The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (now The Rockefeller University), the Rockefeller Foundation, and other philanthropic organizations working nationally and internationally in the fields of education, religion, and health. Rockefeller's total donations to philanthropic endeavors are estimated to have been $540 million.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (JDR Jr.) joined his father's office on October 1, 1897. He oversaw the expansion and diversification of the philanthropic work begun by his father. During his lifetime, the younger Rockefeller gave more than $537 million to educational, religious, cultural, medical, and other charitable projects.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and his wife, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (1874-1948), passed the Rockefeller philanthropic impulse on to their children. John D. 3rd (1906-1978), Nelson A. (1908-1979), Laurance S. (1910-2004), Winthrop (1912-1973), and David (1915-2017) further expanded and diversified Rockefeller influence and interests, establishing their own philanthropic organizations, most notably the Rockefeller Brothers Fund (1940), and becoming more active politically.
In the period following the Second World War, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s sons returned from service to assume an increasing role in family business and philanthropic endeavors, even as they were pursuing their own careers and interests. The office provided family members with a range of services from routine office support (office space, staffing, purchasing, payroll and accounting, travel, security) to specialized investment, economic and philanthropic advising, legal counsel, a library collection, and a public relations staff.
To support their broad activity – a 1951 list of the family's associations detailed more than seventy organizations in which the five Rockefeller brothers actively participated in a business or philanthropic capacity – the family had long relied on a system of associates who worked with individual family members and provided specialized assistance and advice. The Rockefeller family office was originally located at 26 Broadway in the Standard Oil Building, but it moved to Rockefeller Center when the RCA Building opened in the fall of 1933. The family office occupied the 56th floor (and eventually the 54th and 55th floors) of the RCA Building, and was often known as Room 5600. Rockefeller philanthropies such as the American Conservation Association, the Rockefeller Brothers Fund and the Sealantic Fund also operated out of the family office space, and many affiliated businesses (such as Eastern Air Lines and Rockresorts, Inc.) were neighboring Rockefeller Center tenants.
Scope and Contents
This set of general files chronicles management of the philanthropic affairs of David Rockefeller during the period 1992-1996. when he was naturally beginning to curtail his activities.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Albeit to a lesser extent David Rockefeller continued philanthropic activities in many of the Rockefeller's traditional areas of giving. Major interests in these 1992-1996 include but are not limited to: economics, education, international relations, medicine, politics, social welfare, youth programs and camps.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, audio and video tapes, and printed material.
Westchester County (N.Y.); Agriculture; Philanthropy; Philanthropy -- New York (N.Y.); Social problems; Social sciences; Social service; Philanthropy -- New York (State); Philanthropy -- United States; Charitable contributions; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; International relations -- United States; Economics; International relations; Charities -- Investments; Women; Hospitals; Charities; Civic improvement; Arts; Performing arts; United States; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Restoration and conservation; Art; Environmental sciences; Child welfare
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, 44; 54.6 Cubic Feet 42 standard record storage boxes.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  1992-1996
  - A, 1992-1996; 1
    - A. Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appeals - Domestic - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
    - Appeals - Foreign - A-K (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Appeals - Foreign - L-Z (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Applicants - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Aviation - A-Z (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Arts, 1992-1996; 2
    - Arts - A (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Arts - B-Z (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - American Center for Students and Artists Paris, France (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - American Federation of the Arts (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - American Friends of Canada (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Century Association - A-Z (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Children's Art Carnival (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art Long Island City, NY (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - International Foundation for Art Research (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Lincoln Center - A-Z (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln Center - Lincoln Center Theatre (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Center - Contributions (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Municipal Art Society (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Public Art Fund, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Royal Academy Trust (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Skystone Foundation (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Studio in a School Association, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - World Monuments Fund (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dance - A-N (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Dance - O-Z (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dance - Bavarian State Ballet (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Dance - Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dance - Dance Theatre of Harlem - Luncheon, 1993 April 28 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dance - Dance Theatre of Harlem - Luncheon that was Canceled, 1993 March 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dance - Kaatsbaan International Dance Center (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dance - New York City Ballet (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Films - A-Z (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Galleries - A-Z (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Libraries - A-Z (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - Libraries - George Bush Presidential Library Center (Foundation) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Libraries - Center for the Study of the Presidency (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Libraries - Library of Congress (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Libraries - New York Public Library (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Libraries - New York Public Library - Brooke Russell Astor Award (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Memorials - A-Z (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Museums - A-B (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Museums - C-Z (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - Museums - American Museum of Natural History (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Brooklyn Museum (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Museums - The Brooklyn Children's Museum (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Farnsworth Art Museum, Rockland, Maine (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Museums - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Museums - The Frick Collection, New York, NY (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Intercultural (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Museums - Intrepid Museum Foundation (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Contributions (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Museums - Museo Amparo, Pueblo, Mexico (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Museums - Museum for African Art (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Museum of the City of New York (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, CA (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Museums - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - A-Z (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - Chairman's Council (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - Masterpieces from the David and Peggy Rockefeller Collection: Manet - Picasso Exhibit (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Museums - The Museum of Television and Radio (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Museums - National Building Museum (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Portland Museum of Art (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Rijksmuseum, Amsterdam, Netherlands (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Museums - School of American Research (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - A-Z (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution Libraries (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution Archives of American Art Arts (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of the American Indian (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 14, Folder 1-3, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of the American Indian - Contributions (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Studio Museum in Harlem (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Music - A-S (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
    - Music - T-Z (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Music - Boston Symphony Orchestra (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Music - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Music - Carnegie Hall Society (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Music - The Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Music - Metropolitan Opera Association (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Music - Music Assistance Fund (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Music - Philharmonic Symphony Society of New York (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Painting - A-Z (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Poetry - A-Z (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Publications - A-Z (Box 19, Folder 2-5)
    - Publications - Acknowledgment of Books - A-Z (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Publications - Committee to Protect Journalists (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Restorations - A-Z (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Restorations - George C. Marshall Home Preservation Fund, Inc. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Restorations - New York Landmarks Conservancy (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Restorations - Preservation League of New York State (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Restorations - Save Venice, Inc. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Restorations - Vielles Maisons Françaises (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sculpture - A-Z (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Theatre - A-Z (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - B-C, 1992-1996; 3
    - B - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - C - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Civic, 1992-1996; 4
    - Civic - A-Z (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Alpha Center (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - League of Women Voters of the City of New York (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - National Community Reinvestment Corporation (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - National Ethic Coalition of Organization (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - National Executive Service Corps (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - People for the American Way (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Urban Assembly (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Chamber of Commerce - A-Z (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - New York City - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - New York City - Citizens Committee for New York City, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Citizens Housing and Planning Council (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Citizens Union Foundation (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Community Preservation Corporation (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New York City - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York City - Friends of Queen Catherine, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York City - Global Trade and Information Center (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York City - Harlem Educational Activities Fund, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York City - Harlem International Trade Center (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - New York City - New York City Police Foundation, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York City (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - New York City - New York City Housing Partnership (Box 25, Folder 5, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - A-Z (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - Contributions (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - Meetings, Annual Meeting, Pocantico Hills, 1993 June 22 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - Privatization Task Force (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - David Rockefeller Fellows Program (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership - Tribute to David Rockefeller in Celebration of his 80th Birthday (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - New York City - New York City Public-Private Initiative (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Park Avenue Malls Holiday Lighting Project (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Regional Plan Association (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - New York City - South Bronx Overall Economic Development Corporation (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Volunteer Consulting Group (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - New York State - A-Z (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - New York State (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - United States Government (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - United States Government - United States Information Agency (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - United States Government - White House Endowment Fund (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
    - United States Government - White Fellows Foundation (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Clubs, 1992-1996; 5
    - Clubs - A-Z (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
    - Bohemian Grove Club (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - The Harbor Club (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1992-1996; 6
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-Z (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
    - Contributions (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Commercial Ventures, 1992-1996; 7
    - Commercial Ventures - A-E (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - F-Z (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - Investcorp (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Banking - A-Z (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank - A-S (Box 32, Folder 2-4)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank - T-Z (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank - Global Investment Forum, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2-4)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank - International Advisory Committee - A-Z (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Conservation, 1992-1996; 8
    - Conservation - A-M (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
    - Conservation - N-Z (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - René Dubos Center for Human Environments (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Monterey Bay Aquarium (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Northern Forest Alliance (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Student Conservation Association, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - United States of Government (USG) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - A-Z (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - A-Z (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Acadia National Park (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Acadia National Park - A-Z (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous States - A-Z (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous States - Alaska - The Sail Alaska Fund (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - A-Z (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Island Institute (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - New York State - A-Z (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
    - New York State - Rockefeller State Park Preserve (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - New York State - Scenic Hudson (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Parks - A-Z (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Parks - The Parks Council (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Foreign - A-Z (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Foreign - Conservation International (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Recreation - A-Z (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
    - Recreation - Chess in the Schools (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - D-E, 1992-1996; 9
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Defense - A-Z (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - E - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Economics, 1992-1996; 10
    - Economics - A-M (Box 38, Folder 5-8)
    - Economics - N-Z (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Business Council of National Issues (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Business Enterprise Trust (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - The Concord Coalition (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - European Institute of Business Administration (INSEAD) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Hong Kong (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - International Academy of Management (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Institute for International Economics (Box 40, Folder 6, Box 41, Folder 1-4)
    - Institute for International Economics - Contributions (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) (Box 42, Folder 2-4)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) - A-Z (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
    - Royal Economic Society (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Contributions (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) - US Council of the Mexico-US Business Committee (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Education, 1992-1996; 11
    - Education - A-F (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
    - Education - G-Z (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 44, Folder 4, Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Educational Alliance, Inc. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Esalen Institute (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Public Administration (Box 45, Folder 4-5, Box 46, Folder 1)
    - National Center for Learning Disabilities (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Simon Wiesenthal Center (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - A-B (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - C-Q (Box 47, Folder 1-5)
    - Colleges - R-Z (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - American School of Classical Studies at Athens (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - American University of Beirut (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - American University in Cairo (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Americas Fund for Independent Universities (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Barnard College, New York, NY (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Beirut University College, Beirut Lebanon (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Brown University (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Cambridge College, Cambridge, MA (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - A-Z (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Colby College (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - A-Z (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Oral History Research Project and Office (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Teachers College (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Emory University, Atlanta, GA (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Georgetown University, Washington, DC (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - A-Z (Box 51, Folder 3-5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Art Museum (Fogg Art Museum) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - College Fund (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Charitable Remainder Trust (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Contributions (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John King Fairbank Center for East Asian Research (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Fundraising - The University Campaign (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government - Harvard Project on American Indian Economic Development (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies - David Rockefeller Luncheon, 1994 May 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Michael Clark Rockefeller Memorial Fellowship (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Phillips Brooks House Association (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Signet Society (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - International College, Beirut, Lebanon (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Marymount College, Tarrytown, NY (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - New York University (NYU) - A-Z (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - State University of New York (SUNY) - A-Z (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - State University of New York (SUNY) - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government (Box 55, Folder 1)